let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question: "According to the Aufbau principle, electrons occupy orbitals with ________ energies first.",
    answer: "lower",
    options: [
      "higher",
      "lower",
      "equal",
      "opposite"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question: "The order in which electrons are filled in atomic orbitals as per the Aufbau principle is:",
    answer: "1s, 2s, 2p, 3s, 3p, 4s, 3d, 4p, 5s, 4d, 5p, 6s, 4f, 5d, 6p, 7s, 5f, 6d, 7p",
    options: [
      "1s, 2s, 2p, 3s, 3p, 4s, 3d, 4p, 5s, 4d, 5p, 6s, 4f, 5d, 6p, 7s, 5f, 6d, 7p",
      "1s, 2s, 2p, 3s, 3p, 4s, 3d, 4p, 5s, 4d, 5p, 6s, 6p, 7s, 7p",
      "1s, 2s, 3s, 4s, 5s, 6s, 7s",
      "1s, 2p, 3s, 4d, 5p, 6f, 7d"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "The Pauli exclusion principle states that a maximum of ________ electrons can fit in an orbital.",
    answer: "two",
    options: [
      "one",
      "two",
      "three",
      "four"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Hund's rule states that every orbital in a given subshell is singly occupied by electrons before:",
    answer: "a second electron is filled in an orbital",
    options: [
      "a second electron is filled in an orbital",
      "a third electron is filled in an orbital",
      "a new subshell is started",
      "a higher energy orbital is filled"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "The electron configuration of oxygen is:",
    answer: "1s2 2s2 2p4",
    options: [
      "1s1",
      "1s2 2s2 2p4",
      "2s2 2p4",
      "1s2 2s2 2p2"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Exceptions to the Aufbau principle can be explained by the stability provided by:",
    answer: "half-filled or completely filled subshells",
    options: [
      "opposite spin electrons",
      "higher energy orbitals",
      "half-filled or completely filled subshells",
      "equal values for all four quantum numbers"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "According to the Pauli exclusion principle, if two electrons have the same values for all four quantum numbers, they must have ________ spins.",
    answer: "opposite",
    options: [
      "the same",
      "opposite",
      "random",
      "variable"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Hund's rule states that electrons in orbitals with one electron have ________ spin.",
    answer: "the same",
    options: [
      "opposite",
      "the same",
      "random",
      "variable"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "The electron configuration of hydrogen is:",
    answer: "1s1",
    options: [
      "1s1",
      "1s2",
      "2s2 2p4",
      "2s1 2p2"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "The electron configuration of chlorine can also be written as:",
    answer: "[Ne]3s23p5",
    options: [
      "1s2 2s2 2p4",
      "2s2 2p4",
      "1s22s22p63s23p5",
      "[Ne]3s23p5"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 11,
    question: "The atomic number of an element represents the number of ________ in an atom.",
    answer: "protons",
    options: [
      "neutrons",
      "protons",
      "electrons",
      "nucleons"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 12,
    question: "The energy of an orbital is calculated by the sum of the ________ quantum numbers.",
    answer: "principal and azimuthal",
    options: [
      "principal and magnetic",
      "azimuthal and spin",
      "principal and azimuthal",
      "magnetic and spin"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 13,
    question: "The order of filling atomic orbitals according to the Aufbau principle is primarily determined by the ________ quantum number.",
    answer: "principal",
    options: [
      "azimuthal",
      "magnetic",
      "spin",
      "principal"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 14,
    question: "The maximum number of electrons that can fit in the 3d subshell is:",
    answer: "10",
    options: [
      "2",
      "6",
      "10",
      "14"
    ]
  },
  {
  numb: 15,
  question: "The electron configuration of nitrogen is:",
  answer: "1s2 2s2 2p3",
  options: [
    "1s2 2s2 2p4",
    "1s2 2s2 2p3",
    "2s2 2p4",
    "1s2 2s1 2p3"
  ]
},
]
